

### **CONTACT**



+57 3002474408



jpdlamarck@gmail.com



github.com/Zeroluffs

## **SOCIAL NETWORKS**



jhonerpineda



Jhoner DLamarck



@jdlamarck

## **SKILLS**

Python

Power BI

• • • •

Java

# **JHONER PINEDA**

#### Software Engineer

Full Stack developer. I specialize using the MERN stack and I have acquired some previous experience using Angular for Frontend. For backend I have also used Django and GraphQL for my personal projects and Spring Boot professionally. In addition to being experienced in Non-Relational Databases I have professional experience with MySQL and Postgres. Additionally I love Python and tinkering with data sets because I am a big data and ML enthusiast.

## **JOB EXPERIENCE**

#### **Software Engineer-Lovepop**

From January 2022 - July 2022

Helped develop features on the e-Commerce site meant to increase revenue per session such as Send a Surprise, Upsells and improve site usability and accesibility,

- A/B Feature testing.
- · Shipped high-quality code with a focus on scalability, performance, and accessibility.
- · Contribuited in refactoring the code base to use Typescript

#### **Software Developer-Indra**

From September 2021 - January 2022

Developing new solutions for Onesait products and giving support to current ones such as the Customers platform.

- Migrating web modules from AngularJS to ExtJS.
- · Creation of Restful APIs with Spring Boot.
- · Various in house React forms.

## **Junior Software Developer- Proteccion S.A**

From February 2021 to August 2021

Built several responsive features using React, React-Dashboard and Redux. Managed endpoints in the back-end using Django to retrieve data for the front-end.

## **EDUCATION**

Universidad del Norte, Barranquilla

Systems Engineering 2016-2021

## **ADDITIONAL COURSES AND EDUCATION**

#### **Amazon Web Services**

Getting Started with AWS Machine Learning-2021

## **University of Michigan**

Understanding and Visualizing Data with Python - 2020